<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="plugName">Back Power Building</string>
           
           <string name="act_title_breathcontrolpose">Breath Control in Thunderbolt Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_breathcontrolpose">To enter the pose, begin by kneeling on the floor. Lower the hips and buttocks to sit on top of the heels on an exhale. Sit up tall and activate the core muscles, arms relax on the tops of the thighs or along the sides of the body, with the palms down.\n</string>           
           <string name="act_title_catandcow">Cat and Cow</string>
           <string name="act_text_catandcow">Now come up to your hands and knees, making sure your wrists are under your shoulders and your knees are under your hips. We will do 3 rounds of cat and cow. Exhale as you round the spine and tuck the chin. Inhale as you dip the belly and lift the gaze. Exhale for cat pose, rounding the spine and pulling the abs in. Inhale, dip the belly, lift the tailbone, and lift the chin toward the sky. Stretch out your breath each time you flow through cat and cow. Make the breath long and smooth to match your movement. Use your abs and squeeze your glutes each time you come into cat pose. \n\nFeel your whole spine moving through cat and cow, flexion and extension, from the tailbone to the crown of the head. Breathe as you flow. Bring your big toes to touch and sit your hips on your heels in child's pose for a short rest. Relax your forehead onto the mat. Slow down your breath and quiet your mind. When you're ready, rise back to your hands and knees, and we'll do another round of cat and cow. \n\nExhaling as you round your spine into cat, inhaling as you dip the belly into cow. Long, smooth breaths. Imagine your tailbone and crown of your head reaching the peak of the movement at the same moment. Mindful, flowing, and meditative, as you listen to your breath. \n\nThis exercise is great for your spinal health, as well as the strength of your hips and abs. Just a couple more times in this round. And sit the hips on the heels in child's pose for a rest. Relax your spine, relax your hips. Inhale, come back up to hands and knees. \n\nWe'll do one final round of cat and cow. As you round your spine into cat pose, squeeze your glutes as you tuck your hips under. Long, slow breaths and mindful movements. In and out, full flexion and extension through the spine. Stay present with your body here, feeling all the sensations. Great job. One last time. And sit the hips on the heels, returning to child's pose for a rest.\n</string>           
           <string name="act_title_catposevariation">Cat Pose Variation</string>
           <string name="act_text_catposevariation">Round your spine into cat pose, hugging the abdomen in. Press the tops of the feet onto the mat and lift the knees off the ground. Spread the fingers, and press into the mat, supporting the wrists. Breathe and engage the abdominals.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_sphinxpose">Sphinx Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_sphinxpose">Inhale and rise up to hands and knees. Make your way onto your forearms and lower down onto your belly. Point your toes behind you so the tops of your feet are resting on the mat. Face your palms down on the floor with elbows under shoulders. This is sphinx pose. With palms planted on the mat, gently draw your elbows back and draw the heart forward. Lift your chin slightly and feel an opening in the upper back. Let your hips feel totally relaxed on the mat. If you have any lower back pain, engage your abs slightly. Pull the belly button up and in. Take long slow breaths. Breathe down into any areas that feel tense or tight. Imagine those areas expanding with your inhale, creating more space, more openness. And imagine those areas relaxing with your exhale, softening away that tension. Draw the elbows back, pull the heart forward. Squeeze the shoulder blades together on the back. Just a couple more breaths. \n</string>           
           <string name="act_title_oneleggedlocustvariation1r">One-Legged Locust Variation（Right）</string>
           <string name="act_text_oneleggedlocustvariation1r">Stretch the arms forward. Lift the left arm and right leg into the air. Press down on the floor with the right hand and left foot. Lift the chest. Lengthen the spine. Gaze down, tucking the chin and lengthening the spine. </string>           
           <string name="act_title_oneleggedlocustvariation2l">One-Legged Locust Variation（Left）</string>
           <string name="act_text_oneleggedlocustvariation2l">Stretch the arms forward. Lift the right arm and left leg into the air. Press down on the floor with the left hand and right foot. Lift the chest. Lengthen the spine. Gaze down, tucking the chin and lengthening the spine. </string>           
           <string name="act_title_fulllocustvariation">Full Locust Variation</string>
           <string name="act_text_fulllocustvariation">Lift both arms and legs into the air. Keep the knees straight. Reach the arms out. Gaze down and breathe the belly against the mat, gently rocking the body. </string>           
           <string name="act_title_upwardfacingdog">Upward Facing Dog</string>
           <string name="act_text_upwardfacingdog">Back coming into plank. Lower the knees bend the elbows lowering the chest and inhale scoop the heart to upward facing dog. \n\nPressing on the top of feet and lifting legs as you open the heart and gaze upward. Fingers are spread, legs and hips are lifted.\n</string>           
           <string name="act_title_downwardfacingdog">Downward Facing Dog</string>
           <string name="act_text_downwardfacingdog">Inhale, come back up to hands and knees. Tuck your toes under and exhale, lift the hips up and back to downward facing dog. Lift the tailbone high toward the sky and sink the heels toward the mat. Press your chest back toward the thighs and relax your neck. Lengthen your breath here in down dog. Press firmly into the mat with both palms, spreading the fingers. \n</string>           
           <string name="act_title_childspose">Child's Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_childspose">Now slide the left knee back to meet the right and touch the big toes together. Sit your hips on your heels, coming to child's pose and relax your forehead onto the mat. Relax your spine and your hips. \n\nClose your eyes and connect with your breath. Feel the belly press against the thighs with your inhale, softening and expanding the low back. Feel your whole body relax a little more with your exhale. Quiet your thoughts, just being with your body.\n</string>           
           <string name="act_title_sidestretchchildspose1r">Side Stretch Child's Pose (Right)</string>
           <string name="act_text_sidestretchchildspose1r">Turn your chest to the right and fold the torso over the right knee. Reach the arms out and relax the head down. Feel the stretch in your left side body. Keep the hips centered.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_sidestretchchildspose2l">Side Stretch Child's Pose (Left)</string>
           <string name="act_text_sidestretchchildspose2l">Turn your chest to the left and fold the torso over the left knee. Reach the arms out and relax the head down. Feel the stretch in your right side body. Keep the hips centered.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_halfboatpose">Half Boat Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_halfboatpose">Come to seated with the knees bent and feet planted. Lean back and lift the feet off the ground, keeping the knees bend. Reach the arms out next to the legs. Engage the abdomen, open the chest, and draw the shoulders down and back.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_boatpose">Boat Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_boatpose">Bend your knees and we'll do boat pose, an ab exercise. Place your hands behind the thighs and lift the toes off the ground. If you have the strength, reach your arms out next to your legs. Shins are parallel to the ground. Squeeze the abs in, keep breathing, relax your shoulders. \n\nYou can keep your hands on your thighs for more support. Deep breaths, you're doing great. Strong core, squeeze the knees together. And release.\n</string>           
           <string name="act_title_seatedforwardfold">Seated Forward Fold</string>
           <string name="act_text_seatedforwardfold">Stretch the legs straight out in front of you. Inhale raise the arms overhead, exhale hinge at the hips and fold forward over the legs. If this causes pain to the low back, keep the spine long and flat, reaching the chest toward the toes. Relax the back, neck, and head if it's comfortable. Breathe and relax.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_supinespinaltwist1r">Supine Spinal Twist（Left）</string>
           <string name="act_text_supinespinaltwist1r">Come to lie down on your back. Draw the left knee into the chest, straightening the right leg out on the ground. Roll onto your right hip, crossing the left leg over the body. Reach the left arm out, coming into a twist. Turn your gaze to the left. Relax the belly and back. Breathe and twist. </string>           
           <string name="act_title_supinespinaltwist2l">Supine Spinal Twist（Right） </string>
           <string name="act_text_supinespinaltwist2l">Come to lie down on your back. Draw the right knee into the chest, straightening the left leg out on the ground. Roll onto your left hip, crossing the right leg over the body. Reach the right arm out, coming into a twist. Turn your gaze to the right. Relax the belly and back. Breathe and twist. </string>           
           <string name="act_title_supinelowbackmassage">Supine Low Back Massage</string>
           <string name="act_text_supinelowbackmassage">Hug the knees into the chest, wrapping your hands over the shins. Rock the knees forward and backward, side to side, or in circles, massaging the low back on the mat. </string>           
           <string name="act_title_reclinedboundanglepose">Reclined Bound Angle Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_reclinedboundanglepose">Lie down on your back comfortably. Bend your knees, planting the feet on the mat. Then place the soles of your feet together and open the knees in reclined bound angle pose. Touch your thumbs and pointer fingers together in gyan mudra, resting the backs of your hands on the ground. \n\nClose your eyes and connect with your breath. Just relax here, and feel your body softening into gravity. Feel the support of the earth beneath you as you let go. Calm your mind, listening to your breath and feeling the belly expand as you breathe in and relax as you breathe out. Long, mindful, soothing breaths. </string>           
           <string name="act_title_corpsepose">Corpse Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_corpsepose">Now extend your legs straight out on the ground, preparing for shavasana, final relaxation. Turn your palms upward with your arms down at your sides and tuck each shoulder blade flat under your back. Let your feet fall open in a natural way as the legs and hips relax. Tuck your chin slightly, lengthening the back of your neck, and take a swallow to relax your throat. \n\nClose your eyes and start to relax your entire body toward the mat. Relax your face, eyes, and jaw. Relax your throat, neck, and shoulders. Relax your chest, back, and belly. Relax your hips, legs, arms. Relax your hands and feet. Feel your whole body sinking toward the mat and allow yourself to let go completely. Give yourself these few moments where your body can rest and restore, integrating the benefits of your yoga practice. Great job in this session. Namaste.\n</string>
    <!-- ============================================================================= -->
    <string name="session_info_instructor">Instructor: Lucy</string>
    <string name="session_info_class_level">Class Level: Beginner</string>
    <string name="session_info_goal">Goal: Weight Loss</string>
    <string name="session_info">1</string>
    <string name="session_info_like">Back Power Building</string>

    <string-array name="session_keys">
        <item>session_20.xml</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="session_title">
        <item>18 min</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="session_content">
        <item>Casual</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="session_icons">
        <item>small</item>

    </string-array>
    <integer name="actVersion">0</integer>
</resources>