<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="plugName">Basic Strength and Focus</string>
           
           <string name="act_title_standingsidebend1l">Standing Side Bend (Left)</string>
           <string name="act_text_standingsidebend1l">Begin in mountain pose, Tadasana, with your feet hip width apart. Spread your toes and engage your legs. Bring your hands onto your hips. Inhale reach the right arm overhead. Stand tall.\n\nExhale side bend to your left, reaching the right arm over your ear. Engage your core slightly, pulling the belly button in. Instead of rolling the right shoulder forward, draw it back, turning your heart toward the sky. Inhale rise to center. Exhale side bend left. \n\nInhale come to center, exhale curve the body left. Continue flowing with your breath, stretching the right side of your body. Come back to center and exhale relax the right arm</string>           
           <string name="act_title_standingsidebend2r">Standing Side Bend (Right)</string>
           <string name="act_text_standingsidebend2r">Now inhale lift your left arm overhead. Exhale curve the body to the right. Inhale come to center, exhale curve the body right, stretching the left side of the body. Keep flowing with your breath, lifting the heart upward. Exhale come to center and relax the arms down.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_dynamicwidelegchairpose">Dynamic Wide Leg Chair Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_dynamicwidelegchairpose">Good, now step your feet a little bit wider than hip width. Stack your forearms in front of your chest at shoulder height. Engage your core, pulling the belly button in. Bend the knees deeply. Bring your weight into your heels and tuck your tailbone. \n\nInhale straighten the knees slightly, exhale squat back down. Begin pulsing up and down with your breath, inhaling to come up, exhaling to bend down. Engage your core, feel your thighs working. Keep your spine long and flat.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_kneelbendingforwardfold">Bent Knee Forward Fold</string>
           <string name="act_text_kneelbendingforwardfold">Good, exhale fold forward, keeping your knees bent. Rest your chest on your thighs. Bent the knees enough to get your hands on the mat and your chest resting on your thighs. Relax your neck and head down. Feel a gentle stretch in the back of your legs. Breathe and relax. Feel your low back releasing tension.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_twistedarmstretchinlungepose1r">Twisting Low Lunge Pose (Right)</string>
           <string name="act_text_twistedarmstretchinlungepose1r">Inhale lift your gaze forward. Exhale step your left foot back, coming into a lunge position, lowering your left knee to the floor. If your left knee is sensitive, you can place a blanket under the knee for padding. \n\nMake sure the right knee is aligned over the ankle. Inhale raise the spine up. Exhale tuck the tailbone slightly, hugging the abdomen in. Inhale lift the arms to shoulder height. Exhale twist the spine to the right. Keep your arms stretching out to the sides. Squeeze your abdomen in to help you twist. Inhale return to center, exhale twist to the right. Inhale center, exhale twist.\n\n Good, pulse with your breath. Use your core and keep your hips stable. Inhale come to center, exhale relax the arms down, planting the palms. Inhale step the left foot forward, coming to forward fold.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_twistedarmstretchinlungepose2l">Twisting Low Lunge Pose (Left)</string>
           <string name="act_text_twistedarmstretchinlungepose2l">Exhale step the right foot back, lowering the knee to the mat in a low lunge. Keep the left knee over the ankle and lift the spine up. Tuck the tailbone, lengthening the low back. Inhale reach the arms up to shoulder height. Exhale twist the spine to the left. Inhale center and exhale twist. \n\nFlow with your breath, engaging your core. Inhale come to center. Exhale plant the palms. Slide your left knee back next to the right, coming to hands and knees. Align the knees under the hips and the wrists under the shoulders.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_crunchedtigerpose1r">Tiger Pose (Right)</string>
           <string name="act_text_crunchedtigerpose1r">Good, engage your abdomen, lengthening your spine. Gaze down at the mat. Inhale, lift the right leg in the air behind you, pressing back with the heel. Exhale bring your knee toward your nose, rounding your spine and hugging your abs in. Inhale, lengthen the spine and reach the right leg back. \n\nExhale bring the knee toward the nose. Keep pulsing with your breath and see if you can keep the right foot off the ground the whole time. Use the core and use your breath. Good, relax the right knee down.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_crunchedtigerpose2l">Tiger Pose (Left)</string>
           <string name="act_text_crunchedtigerpose2l">Now inhale lift the left leg behind you. Exhale bring your knee to your nose, rounding the spine and hugging the abs in. Keep flowing with your breath, keeping the left leg off the mat the whole time. Press your palms firmly into the mat, spreading your fingers. Exhale come back to center.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_dynamicarmstretchinglucust">Wide-Arm Dynamic Locust Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_dynamicarmstretchinglucust">Great, now come onto your belly. Bring your forehead onto the mat. Stretch your arms out to the sides with the palms down. Lengthen your legs behind you. The feet should be hip width apart and point the toes. As you inhale, lift your arms, legs, and head off the mat, stretching the arms wide. \n\nInstead of lifting the chin, tuck the chin gazing down. Exhale relax down to the mat. Inhale lift, squeezing the back body, exhale lower. Inhale lift, squeezing the glutes, keeping the knees straight. Exhale lower. Inhale sweep the arms out. Exhale relax your body onto the mat.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_armstretchinglucust">Dynamic-Arm Locust Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_armstretchinglucust">Good. Inhale lift up to locust pose. Exhale sweep the hands back by the hips. Inhale stretch the arms to the sides, exhale sweep them back. One more time. Exhale relax to the mat. Take a couple nice, deep breaths here.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_dynamicbackrolling">Dynamic Back Rolling</string>
           <string name="act_text_dynamicbackrolling">Great job. Now make your way onto your back. Bend your knees. Hug the knees into your chest. Wrap your hands over the shins and begin rolling side to side, massaging your low back onto the mat. Relax your shoulders and neck. Take a nice, deep breath. Beautiful. Stretch your legs onto the mat, lying flat on your back. Your hands are down by your hips.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_supinearmstretch">Supine Full Body Stretch</string>
           <string name="act_text_supinearmstretch">Good, now reach your arms overhead by the ears. Relax them down on the mat. Flex your toes toward the sky. Press out with your heels, engaging your thighs. Reach the arms overhead, stretch the fingertips away from the heels for a full body stretch. Take a few deep breaths, seeing how long you can make your body. Good, when you're ready, relax your arms down at your sides once again.</string>           
           <string name="act_title_corpsepose">Corpse Pose</string>
           <string name="act_text_corpsepose">Now let's come into our final resting pose, shavasana. Make yourself as comfortable as possible. Close your eyes when you're ready. Feel your whole body starting to let go and relax. Release any tension from your muscles and allow the earth to hold your body. \n\nEven let your breath flow effortlessly. You can relax here for as long as you'd like. When you're ready, you can open your eyes. Great job today. Namaste.</string>
    <!-- ============================================================================= -->
    <string name="session_info_instructor">Instructor: Sophie</string>
    <string name="session_info_class_level">Class Level: All</string>
    <string name="session_info_goal">Goal: Weight Loss</string>
    <string name="session_info">1</string>
    <string name="session_info_like">Basic Strength and Focus</string>

    <string-array name="session_keys">
        <item>session_10.xml</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="session_title">
        <item>10 min</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="session_content">
        <item>Casual</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="session_icons">
        <item>small</item>

    </string-array>
    <integer name="actVersion">0</integer>
</resources>